tollywoodandhra.in 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Telugu Movie Reviews |Tollywood Latest 2016 News | TollywoodAndhra.in

As per law act Privacy Policy is not required if you don’t want it:  
However, a privacy policy lets your website users know exactly what you do  
with their private information and therefore can help you to build trust between  
your company and your customers. It is always a great way of showing  
confidence and genuineness on your visitors. In other words, it says that we  
care for our visitors.

We may collect information from our users: You may collect information  
when users place an order, sign up for an account, or access certain areas of  
your site.

What information you collect: We collect information from you when you fill up

our forms on feedbacks, comments or respond to a survey in our website.

So you should be always careful in putting authentic names and not automatically  
generated names and data through any software when asked to enter your: name,  
mailing address, phone number, credit card information or social security number.  
You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s  
use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to  
your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART  
cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

How you use the information you collect: Any of the information we collect

from you may be used in one of the following ways: (note :all information are  
confidential and are in no way disclosed)

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(We are continuously trying to showcase the best quality,so any suggestion from  
you will a valuable treasure for us, so that we strive for excellence)

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred,  
or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent,  
other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service  
requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature you follow our  
terms and conditions and acceptable user policy by which our website is abided.

Our website uses cookies:

By using our website and agreeing to these terms and conditions, you consent to  
our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of our [privacy policy]  
These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our  
behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business

We don’t disclose your information to 3rd parties:This does not include trusted  
third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or  
servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate  
to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights,  
property, or safety.

We sometimes may use 3rd party links:  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or  
services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent  
privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and  
activities of these linked sites.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy  
Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of  
age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least  
13 years old or older.

Reserve the rights to change the policy: We are at our free will to change and  
revamp our policies without prior notices, to suite the requirements and updates  
from time to time.

Online Privacy Policy Only:

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website  
and not to information collected offline.

Your agreeing & your Consent:

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

Terms and Conditions:

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers,  
and limitations of liability governing the use of our website .

Contact us if you have any question regarding our privacy policy: contact us  
at admin@tollywoodandhra.in if you have any question regarding any issues of our  
privacy policy.

It's only fair to share...
